{
	"id": 6,
	"title": "Lesson 6",
	"description": "Talk about family and people",
	"content": [
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Mo", "ser apel Anya."],
			"answer": "ti",
			"options": ["ti", "to", "fami"],
			"translation": "My little sister is called Anya."
		},
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Li ena", "frer ek ene ser."],
			"answer": "trwa",
			"options": ["trwa", "gran", "ti"],
			"translation": "He has three brothers and one sister."
		},
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Eski to", "frer travay laba?"],
			"answer": "gran",
			"options": ["mo", "to", "gran"],
			"translation": "Does your big brother work there?"
		},
		{
			"type": "match",
			"options": {
				"mother": "mama",
				"father": "papa",
				"daughter": "tifi",
				"son": "garson"
			}
		},
		{
			"type": "match",
			"options": {
				"sister": "ser",
				"brother": "frer",
				"family": "fami",
				"person": "dimoun"
			}
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'sister'?",
			"answer": "ser",
			"options": ["tifi", "ser", "mama"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'brother'?",
			"answer": "frer",
			"options": ["frer", "papa", "dimoun"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'family'?",
			"answer": "fami",
			"options": ["mama", "fami", "ser"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'person'?",
			"answer": "dimoun",
			"options": ["frer", "tifi", "dimoun"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'has'?",
			"answer": "ena",
			"options": ["to", "ena", "mo"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "I have a brother",
			"answer": "Mo ena ene frer",
			"options": ["Mo", "frer", "ene", "ena", "ser"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "She has two sisters",
			"answer": "Li ena de ser",
			"options": ["ser", "Li", "de", "ena", "tifi"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "To ena ene papa",
			"answer": "You have a father",
			"options": ["father", "You", "have", "a", "girl"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "Mo fami ena trwa dimoun",
			"answer": "My family has three people",
			"options": ["people", "has", "family", "My", "three", "two"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "Li ena ene tifi",
			"answer": "He has a daughter",
			"options": ["daughter", "He", "a", "has", "son"]
		}
	],
	"vocabulary": {
		"mother": "mama",
		"father": "papa",
		"son": "garson",
		"daughter": "tifi",
		"sister": "ser",
		"brother": "frer",
		"family": "fami",
		"person": "dimoun",
		"have": "ena",
		"one": "ene",
		"two": "de",
		"three": "trwa",
		"my": "mo",
		"your": "to",
		"his/her": "li"
	}
}
